vidbliss.com 2014-02-09

# vidbliss - Watch Movies Instantly Online

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Iamatic Consulting. So we’ve developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Iamatic Consulting or a Iamatic Consulting affiliated company. Iamatic Consulting and its affiliates may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising.

Here are some examples of the types of personal information Iamatic Consulting may collect and how we may use it.

#### What personal information we collect

When you create an Iamatic Consulting account, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information. 

#### How we use your personal information

  * The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Iamatic Consulting’s latest product announcements, software updates, and upcoming events. It also helps us to improve our services, content, and advertising.
  * We also use personal information to help us develop, deliver, and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. 
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with Iamatic Consulting, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.
  * We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Iamatic Consulting’s products, services, and customer communications. 

#### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as language, zip code, area code, location, and the time zone where a Iamatic Consulting product is used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services, and advertising. 

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

#### Cookies and Other Technologies

Iamatic Consulting’s website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

As is true of most websites, we gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Iamatic Consulting may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

#### Protection of Personal Information

Iamatic Consulting takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

#### Integrity and Retention of Personal Information

Iamatic Consulting makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

#### Access to Personal Information

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at vidbliss.com. For other personal information, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access so you can request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Iamatic Consulting is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. 

#### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

#### Links to Other Sites

Iamatic Consulting websites contains links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of personal information may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate with reputable websites, Iamatic Consulting cannot be responsible for the information handling practices of these other websites. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully.
